ANUSHKA MAHALEKAMGE | WEB DEVELOPER

Etobicoke, Ontario | 647-767-3680 | anushka.amila@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Solution-oriented and problem solver with 7+ years of experience building and maintaining highperformance web sites and applications. With a solid background in web development, I'm a self motivated, results-driven, collaborative web developer with a focus on delivering exceptional solutions that meet business objectives.

Detailed resume & portfolio at : www.anushkamahalekamge.dev

CORE COMPETENCIES

- ✓ Develop, manage websites/applications
- Web tracking, SEO and security optimizations
- Programming languages (PHP, JavaScript, ..)
 Agile software development
- Front-end technologies (HTML, SCSS, etc)
 Test driven development & UI, UX enhancements
- CMS web development (WordPress, etc.)
- Source control
- Responsive web development (Bootstrap..)
- Server management
- ✓ Web UI design & UX enhancements
- Improve web traffic and run media campaigns

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Aegiz Wireless- Etobicoke, Canada

Web Developer | October, 2021 - Present

- Develop, Oversee and maintain inventory management system
- Develop and maintain the other company websites which are built on CMS platforms
- Collaborate with the team and run campaigns to promote different products
- Analyze the traffic, improve UI/UX and optimize websites for speed & SEO

Enfection Pvt Ltd - Colombo, Sri Lanka

Associate lead web development | August, 2016 - August, 2021

- Attended client meetings, gather requirements and helped plan the project timelines
- Lead the team assign tasks and overlooked projects
- Developed, optimized and maintained custom build web applications and CMS projects
- Enhanced web application security and search engine optimization

Traverse Lanka Tours - Kandana, Sri Lanka

Web Administrator | January, 2014 - July, 2016

- Built and maintained websites of the company and researched on new platforms & methods to improve bookings
- Improved SEO, engaged on content planning and building traffic
- · lead marketing campaigns on social media & paid media

EDUCATION

2021 - 2022 | Conestoga Collage, Kitchener Postgraduate Certificate - Web Development

Certificate - Web Engineering

2012 | Advanced Technology Center(ATC)

2012 - 2014 | British Computer Society

2011 | IDM, Colombo

BCS Higher Education Qualification

Certificate - Web Designing